Aiko Cheslin

Summary

I have excelled for 5 years founding technical start ups and I am excited to apply that experience. I live for solving technical problems as much as interpersonal problems. I have founded and led 3 hackathon teams to victory over the last 2 years. I enjoy participating in the growth and development of others. I am looking for opportunities to tackle complex problems.

Skills

Languages: C#, JavaScript, Ruby

Frameworks: ASP.Net MVC 5, jQuery, Meteor, Rails, Twitter Bootstrap

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

Technologies: Sublimetext 3, Visual Studio 2013 Other: HTML 5, CSS 3/Less, Linux, Docker.io, Git

Experience

apollobit | Front End Developer

Present

Development of data-intensive interfaces in Groovy, GSP, jQuery, Bootstrap, Less and D3

LucidPaper Consulting | Founder

Jan. 2011 - Present

 Providing technical marketing and advanced custom solutions for Reactive Website Development, Social Media / Text Message Marketing, Search Engine / Location-Based Marketing Optimization

onCater | Director of Business Dev.

Apr. 2014 - Present

- Prospecting a customer pipeline worth \$750,000 annually.
- Development of a sales automation integrating Insightly, Fullcontact, Google calendar, Gmail and TimeTrader

Rental Kharma | Director of Sales

Feb. 2013 – July 2013

- Managed and recruited a sales team of four
- Developed commercial-facing finical service business vertical

Live Fitness Technologies | Co-Founder & CTO

May 2012 – Oct. 2012

 Developed a real time video communication platform using Ruby on Rail, webRTC, ¡Query, Bootstrap and Less

Education

SeedPaths | Software development boot camp Agile 42 | Scrum Master Certification Nov. 2014

Nov. 2014

Seedpaths.com/Aiko-Cheslin

AikoCheslin@gmail.com

720.432.2456(AIKO)

/lucidpaper

/users/3191423

Digital copy available at: bit.ly/AikoResume

References

References available at bit.ly/AikoReferences

v1.4.3